{
  "easy": [
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of be?",
      "answer": "sum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of be?",
      "answer": "es"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of be?",
      "answer": "est"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of be?",
      "answer": "sumus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of be?",
      "answer": "estis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of be?",
      "answer": "sunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of can?",
      "answer": "possum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of can?",
      "answer": "potes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of can?",
      "answer": "potest"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of can?",
      "answer": "possumus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of can?",
      "answer": "potestis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of can?",
      "answer": "possunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of want?",
      "answer": "volo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of want?",
      "answer": "vis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of want?",
      "answer": "vult"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of want?",
      "answer": "volumus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of want?",
      "answer": "vultis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of want?",
      "answer": "volunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of love?",
      "answer": "amo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of love?",
      "answer": "amas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of love?",
      "answer": "amat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of love?",
      "answer": "amamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of love?",
      "answer": "amatis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of love?",
      "answer": "amant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of see?",
      "answer": "video"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of see?",
      "answer": "vides"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of see?",
      "answer": "videt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of see?",
      "answer": "videmus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of see?",
      "answer": "videtis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of see?",
      "answer": "vident"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of hear?",
      "answer": "audio"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of hear?",
      "answer": "audis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of hear?",
      "answer": "audit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of hear?",
      "answer": "audimus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of hear?",
      "answer": "auditis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of hear?",
      "answer": "audiunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capio"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capimus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens of do?",
      "answer": "ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens of do?",
      "answer": "agis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens of do?",
      "answer": "agit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens of do?",
      "answer": "agimus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens of do?",
      "answer": "agitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens of do?",
      "answer": "agunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does mean not in Latin?",
      "answer": "non"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does come mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "venire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does ask mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "interrogare"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does answer mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "respondere"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does be mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "esse"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does can mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "posse"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does want mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "velle"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does love mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "amare"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does see mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "videre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does hear mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "audire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does do mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "agere"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does and mean in Latin?",
      "answer": "et"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does answer mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "respondere"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does why mean in Latin?",
      "answer": "cur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does what mean in Latin?",
      "answer": "quid"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does sit mean in Latin?(infinitive)",
      "answer": "sedere"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amicus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amici"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amico"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amicum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amico"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amici"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amicorum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amicis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amicos"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of friend(m.)?",
      "answer": "amicis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amica"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicae"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicae"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amica"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicae"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicarum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of friend(f.)?",
      "answer": "amicis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of gift?",
      "answer": "donum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of gift?",
      "answer": "doni"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of gift?",
      "answer": "dono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of gift?",
      "answer": "donum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of gift?",
      "answer": "dono"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of gift?",
      "answer": "dona"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of gift?",
      "answer": "donorum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of gift?",
      "answer": "donis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of gift?",
      "answer": "dona"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of gift?",
      "answer": "donis"
    }
  ],
  "medium": [
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amabam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amabas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amabat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amabamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amabatis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amabant"
    },
     {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum of see?",
      "answer": "videbam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum of see?",
      "answer": "videbas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum of see?",
      "answer": "videbat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum of see?",
      "answer": "videbamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum of see?",
      "answer": "videbatis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum of see?",
      "answer": "videbant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebatis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebant"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebatis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebant"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum of do?",
      "answer": "agebam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum of do?",
      "answer": "agebas"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum of do?",
      "answer": "agebat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum of do?",
      "answer": "agebamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum of do?",
      "answer": "agebatis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum of do?",
      "answer": "agebant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of voice?",
      "answer": "vox"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of voice?",
      "answer": "vocis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of voice?",
      "answer": "voci"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of voice?",
      "answer": "vocem"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of voice?",
      "answer": "voce"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of voice?",
      "answer": "voces"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of voice?",
      "answer": "vocum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of voice?",
      "answer": "vocibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of voice?",
      "answer": "voces"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of voice?",
      "answer": "vocibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of river?",
      "answer": "flumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of river?",
      "answer": "fluminis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of river?",
      "answer": "flumini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of river?",
      "answer": "fluminem"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of river?",
      "answer": "flumine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of river?",
      "answer": "flumines"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of river?",
      "answer": "fluminum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of river?",
      "answer": "fluminibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of river?",
      "answer": "flumines"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of river?",
      "answer": "fluminibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of ship?",
      "answer": "navis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of ship?",
      "answer": "navis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of ship?",
      "answer": "navi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of ship?",
      "answer": "navem"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of ship?",
      "answer": "nave"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of ship?",
      "answer": "naves"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of ship?",
      "answer": "navium"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of ship?",
      "answer": "navibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of ship?",
      "answer": "naves"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of ship?",
      "answer": "navibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of day?",
      "answer": "dies"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of day?",
      "answer": "diei"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of day?",
      "answer": "diei"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of day?",
      "answer": "diem"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of day?",
      "answer": "die"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of day?",
      "answer": "dies"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of day?",
      "answer": "dierum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of day?",
      "answer": "diebus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of day?",
      "answer": "dies"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of day?",
      "answer": "diebus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens passive of love?",
      "answer": "amor"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens passive of love?",
      "answer": "amaris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens passive of love?",
      "answer": "amatur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens passive of love?",
      "answer": "amamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens passive of love?",
      "answer": "amamini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens passive of love?",
      "answer": "amantur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens passive of see?",
      "answer": "videor"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens passive of see?",
      "answer": "videris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens passive of see?",
      "answer": "videtur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens passive of see?",
      "answer": "videmur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens passive of see?",
      "answer": "videmini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens passive of see?",
      "answer": "videntur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audior"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens passive of hear?",
      "answer": "auditur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audimur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audimini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiuntur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capior"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "caperis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capitur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capimur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capimini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiuntur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular praesens passive of do?",
      "answer": "agor"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular praesens passive of do?",
      "answer": "ageris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular praesens passive of do?",
      "answer": "agitur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural praesens passive of do?",
      "answer": "cagimur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural praesens passive of do?",
      "answer": "agimini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural praesens passive of do?",
      "answer": "aguntur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum passive of love?",
      "answer": "amabar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum passive of love?",
      "answer": "amabaris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum passive of love?",
      "answer": "amabatur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum passive of love?",
      "answer": "amabamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum passive of love?",
      "answer": "amabamini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum passive of love?",
      "answer": "amabantur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum passive of see?",
      "answer": "videbar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum passive of see?",
      "answer": "videbaris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum passive of see?",
      "answer": "videbatur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum passive of see?",
      "answer": "videbamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum passive of see?",
      "answer": "videbamini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum passive of see?",
      "answer": "videbantur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebaris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebatur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebamini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum passive of hear?",
      "answer": "audiebantur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebaris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebatur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebamini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum passive of take (capere)?",
      "answer": "capiebantur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular imperfectum passive of do?",
      "answer": "agebar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular imperfectum passive of do?",
      "answer": "agebaris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular imperfectum passive of do?",
      "answer": "agebatur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural imperfectum passive of do?",
      "answer": "agebamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural imperfectum passive of do?",
      "answer": "agebamini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural imperfectum passive of do?",
      "answer": "agebantur"
    }
  ],
  "hard": [
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of sea?",
      "answer": "mare"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of sea?",
      "answer": "maris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of sea?",
      "answer": "mari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of sea?",
      "answer": "mare"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of sea?",
      "answer": "mari"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of sea?",
      "answer": "maria"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of sea?",
      "answer": "marium"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of sea?",
      "answer": "maribus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of sea?",
      "answer": "maria"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of sea?",
      "answer": "maribus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative singular of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratuum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of officer?",
      "answer": "magistratibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive singular of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative singular of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative singular of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative singular of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nominative plural of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornua"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the genitive plural of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornuum"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the dative plural of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the accusative plural of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornua"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ablative plural of cornu?",
      "answer": "cornibus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular perfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amavi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular perfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amavisti"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular perfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amavit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural perfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amavimur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural perfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amavistis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural perfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaverunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person singular plusquamperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaveram"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person singular plusquamperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaveras"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person singular plusquamperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaverat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first person plural plusquamperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaveramus"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second person plural plusquamperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaveratis"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third person plural plusquamperfectum of love?",
      "answer": "amaverant"
    }
  ]
}
